translation
@Fahood_qahtany 0557669038
end of the day
Tony
@Fahood_qahtany
Damn
, "Mike"
be aware
Madam, are you okay?
Are you okay, Madam?
my lady ?
cover me
Edwar from behind
Not Taathrki Aaahrh
Hear
Take the car
Take only what you want
! This idea, my dear
What is your problem?
These things are the enemy, it is assumed
We are in the same side
! There are no longer aspects of the sample
Delivered supplies
Everything very
Difficult to get something
These days
everything
Screw you
Lovely
Now we get her permission
We Nchahdk previous day
Djaltena hungry,
Damn
AAH
You
Men killed fucks
You are, what you want?
For heaven's sake, ammunition Do you want to?
! Take it, take Matrade
No, no, no, do not do
where do you come from ?
Austin, come from Austin damned
Is there more of those things there?
There are all sorts of those damned things
Everywhere, what do you think, man?
is she with you ?
Yeah
We found wandering in the woods
By almost five days
We thought that benefit from them
But we take care of them
Take care of them
I swear to you
As if they were of us
You, hey, where are you going?
You can not leave me here, man that
! No night is approaching
I was trying to just Ange
just like you
Wait
Bitch
Damn
Gosh
! You
Hello
Welcome
Is not this the most beautiful child Trinh?
Yup
What is his name ?
, "Jacob"
, "Jacob Walles, Jr,"
and you what is your name ?
, "Annabel"
, "Well," Annabel
So, we need to get out of here, OK
Well Haya
come with me
Get up
Yes, Come with me
Hey
Hey, wait
Where are you going ?
! Only going
You can not we leave here, we will not survive in the night
In addition you need a safe place when
Night comes
There is no safe place
I'm with a group of survivors
Many of them were policemen
We have, weapons, ammunition, food, water
, "We have even" Electricity
Listen, if you took us there
I promise you there is a safe place for the night
In addition to a lot of food
And ammunition that you can carry it tomorrow
Where is he ?
Dallas, less than an hour and a half
Those things?
Is there too much of it?
Attacking us every night, but
! We can fend them off
! let's go
Come on
I am Sam
an Acronym for "Samantha"
but Everyone call me "the Sam"
"Rourke"
-Is that your name or your title?
! It's beautiful
What do you think the speeches?
Why take care of?
Are you fine ?
Listen, I know I have not the least of there, but
Thank you, for what you did
You do not meet a lot of the righteous
! These days
And what makes you think I righteous?
I want to know any way, take the
We can not survive -Come on
which way? -from here
There, Turn Left
Damn
It was a bad idea
, I Open the door
We are coming
I, you Taatleghana
What's going on, where are you?
, "We are coming from," Comer Street
! They're everywhere
We want you to always prepared for us -
Crushed -
Is he ?
Just go
I made myself a wooden heart
Ki sailed in red blood
They are coming
Moved, I mean moved
Scouts are coming in the car
They locked them in case
Well, my children, let us
You know practice, double the speed of
let's go
Damn Ya, open the gate
We will be with you in seconds
, We go down to the garage O
Yakom Well, you know, practice
Ba quickly but safely
I love you my dear
Come on, come on, come on, come on
Let us, let us
Lose your weapons
Good
! Open it
Come on
From any way?
Come on -
Turn left, this is -
They roar
No kidding
Come on, come
Orkda
locomotive -
Come on -
Moved
Gtona
move
Let us, let us
Moved -
Gtona -
move -
I move -
They moved, they moved
Come on, admitted
No
Lose yourself -
Stand here -
Where ?
HAD -
Oh crushed -
There was a group of Alhjamin
We were ambushed
What the hell is going on here
It can this be?
His name, but otherwise, I would also dead
We should stop bringing Aasam
Otherwise Stjelban wrong type
You're in charge here?
You ?
Where are you, Lord? -New York
New York, here, How come all of this
The road to reach here?
On the road -Alone?
Wait a minute, you're on your own
Since the beginning of the plague?
Yes, baited
Damn you, Tstadhm?
What are you doing ? Kill them all?
There are millions of those damned things
Abroad
Well it's much less
From here to, you bastard -this man is crazy
Oh for heaven's sake, we will not allow
For this man to stay here right?
What are you, a former soldier in the army?
Or convicted?
Regarding that matter
has been guilty of?
I do not mean insult, but was not
A reasonable person, but we accepted
Without an insult? You do not really Taajabina
Not bear the existence of here frankness -
Screw you -
No No listened to
I promised fuel, ammunition
Killed and attacked Sam right
This man may be one of the
Traders who fucks who Hajmuk
And killed -You?
Do you killed my brother, oh son of a bitch?
It will come out of control
Killed my brother, son of a bitch?
! We found the plane
What ?
We found the plane
Outside completely
So it is not far from us
100 miles away
She cargo plane
We will carry each and every one of us
You
! Show me
let's go
Come with us
Move
Here is where we are attacked
Where the plane and here
They're just sitting here waiting for us
What do you think O ?
Can you you fly us
Look good enough
What about Electronics plane?
Thrusters and landing gear looked good
There is nothing to hinder the air -Engines?
Fuel began well for me
There is no water in the water tank
I'm not a high level in the engine
You told me what I'm looking for I have done
This is our best choice
If the plane as you say permission
Yup
Make her fly
Each Maalana to do is to survive at night
And leave at the crack of dawn
And leave this place disappears
Our mirror in the background
In the meantime,
! I apologize but I do not trust you
I do not need to cause problems
! But we will need your weapons
I hope to be able to walk in the water
Ye Olde
Because you need a miracle to sample
For this to happen
You, just give him weapons
I beg you
That was of any consolation it
You Ststaidha
We will adhere to the deal held by the with you
We will give you the fuel
-Ammo -Whatever what you need
But tonight You will be locked in a cell
Heck Thanks
God you
I've given you weapons
What if it was a hoax
Able to enter here
trying to kill us and we are asleep
takin every thing we have
But he saved my life
I have been taking the decision
Let me show you your room
Must be unable Dad
He is a stubborn man
It was so before it happens
This Anyway
The head of the investigators
When the investigation is important
And then we lost safer
oackhe has become one of those
! Things
I think it is somewhat lost
Communication with neighborhoods
Much of this is happening
Yes, then, the whole world
He lost his mind, right?
Let me asking you if
Maljnon in a crazy world?
Do you want to carry my child?
Come on, follow me
So why not cross the Aarvaq
directly To leadership?
It's at least three days to lead the (Baja)
All the families and children
What we Nduom for all this time on the road
oan Did not reach us gangs (Alhjamin)
It was to do those things
It would be as if the bell sounded the dinner
That's why we need that plane -This
You know, we believe that our defenses will bear
I know,khttna had to wait for them
And rebuild
The belief that these things in the end
Will die of starvation
! And that our mistake
So big that launched him in the garage
So who is wearing camouflage uniforms?
Yup -Is a new
Suddenly appeared two weeks ago, three
Huge villain
oho Is a little different
! Watching
We guess that is one of those things led to us
Because they were strongly attacked us every night
From then, man
Kabasir meet in hotel death
And where is that, exactly?
The bakery -
Yup -
About a mile from here
That is infested, man
I hear my friend
Dad sincere in his words, we agreed?
It will implement the agreement
Hey
, Thank you for re
Look on the bright side you,
More safely in the cage
Keep your eyes only him
Sorry for being locked you so
! You
How was the ?
Just like anywhere else
People are dead, dying
! I could not see them ever
I wanted to do it
I Solthak Law School
And get married and fathered children
All those things
, You met
, I was engaged to the little brother
! We were in the house when this happened
Then they said, kept in your homes and shut down your doors
ocetkonowa Safe, so
There were
Two of them were able to enter
And told me to enter the bathroom
And shut the door and Ochtbye
! This is precisely Maflth
otzkr Sitting on the cold ground and only
I cover my ear such a young child is afraid
olcunnina You are unable to hear
All these noises, and then just stopped
And came to and attacked me
But he is no longer that I know
I had forgotten who I am?
If it does not appear to be dead
He was forced to kill his brother
Should not do it anyone, know
Once they turn, it does not matter you by
Try to turn
Faster than the speed to pull the trigger
How do you think it's all that happened?
! A lot of Altakmyat about how this
But it does not matter
! Very clear how the end
, No, there is a colony of survivors in the
It's It's in the middle of the desert
It is isolated
150 miles away from the nearest anything
Even those things quickly, They can not
Accessible, without Ihtrkoa to death first
Give ear to
It does not matter, the amount of distance that Tdaanha
Between you and them
You will find a way
So why come here?
I thought you want to ride that plane?
I did not say it never?
You know
There was something I think about it very much
In the garage
! I saw your face when he closed the door
Moment those sweating Pink
! And between that thing
Do you want to tell me about the reason for that?
Yes, I've taken something from me
And I'll do whatever is required
, Ki Ostaidh
You
I thought I told you that monitored?
My They do what?
Feed a child from a false
Nipple Hiqiqh?
There is nothing wrong, for attained some rest
My will
I can stay if you want
And kept in your company
There is nothing wrong
I will take care -OK
Nothing was left in the world only a few, right?
! Tguetenai will eventually
Nothing in the 3 and 4
ejreb Again O
nothing -
Try again, man -
There's nothing, man
What do we have?
Dad, we do not have broadcast, man
I do not have any cameras
I can not see anything outside the building
No garage, no front entrance
! nothing
Everything, man missing
These Allaina corrupted the cameras -
What are they doing right?
! Whatever it is not good
!!! AAH
! It's at the top
stay here, I will go off
No, no
! You
Are you fine? -
I'm fine -
Go up to the fifth floor and discovered
How did they manage to enter, and close it
I will do that
!! Damn me, it bleeds -I was bitten
!! Wait
Or not '' A good
! We can only cut
I'm sorry, It's too late for that
! Oh man
To do one thing quickly
! We do not have a lot of time
I said wait
Please, for Atflha
In front of my little girl, okay
I want you to go to abroad
With Miss Well?
Your father loves you
!! wait
Put it in the bag
Please, all of us listened
The sun will appear after 4 hours
We agreed ?
To everyone's resting and getting ready to go
With the first light
Tomorrow
We would leave the place
Take your rest
Then opened
OK
! Be prepared
wait wait
Something stuck Maajolh
I do not know
Try again
wait wait
I try again
It is stuck, set off
one more time
wait wait -
!Stop -
Will burn engine
what's going on -
We have to rally around him -
Keep castle -
you got it -
I do not know, something Maymanah
Nothing makes him stuck
Gosh
If that is the cause of all the noise
They do not do such things
Damn
I Ocolkm if we move those cars
Garage door will not move
With all the weight it
No, we will never move Majkova
Of those dirt to get us out before nightfall
If they were caught us with all these people
After Dark
Will everyone of these things
Within miles around
Sitardona all the way to the airport
! If we got there
We will move as we can -Move on
And leave early morning
This building will not last until morning
-No way
If even half that stirred the dirt today
They'd send it back to its place
When it is dark
If they can do that in one day
They can do again
It will take us days to vacate the road
So that we know how to do it
And we have the means
Maalana do is bring cars from abroad
! exactly
We mean only,
Bring something and we hold him our needs
And move on our way
No, man,tlk cars ruined,
Abroad for three years
Stalled batteries, tires empty
I will never be able to find a good car
And enough to get us out of here before sunset
There must be no way
Eliminate their leader
What ?
, So kill the
And the rest of those damned animals
Tear each other to replace whereabouts
how do you know that ?
Because I did it before
That may give you the opportunity you need
To get to that plane
What are you talking about hell
You want to kill them?
Attacking those things is completely
What you need to do the opposite
You know, I try to keep these
People alive
I do not ask these people
joining to ?
How can asking exactly?
gunpowder
Detonators
explosives
Give me those rations that I need
I Sohajm Areen it in their sleep
I was sure
This man will lead us to the graves
Who the hell are even
We listen to you anyway?
And what are you doing here basically?
As for the dreaded Anglq your mouth for once?
Let it sought clarification
You will reach the middle of those things
Kill the in the land in the hope that
Leave the rest confused
For a long enough period
so that we can all Ride our cars fictional
The money 90 miles away
To the plane ?
Right
! Fantastic, I make sure all
So Areen
the hotel
It is 12 floors of the dark
! Night and day
Yes, they are sleeping in herds
On the lower floors in the basement
There where we find them
We know their place
Why not just burn the damn building?
No
Yes I igniting place
But as soon as he wakes up one of those Alohaia and screaming
Sitbosron all Kabasir
, I have to spend on the
This is why the whole thing
For you, right?
! The
You want to get out of here, right?
Ttiroa to this brave new world
Bring me what I want
At the very least it will make it possible for you
You will not go 25 feet
The dreaded hotel
It's a deadly trap
You know and I know
! Time is running out of us
You will die if you stay here
We do not have another option
We have to find those cars
This city was the 2 million people
We can find a sound car
boss
Never it will not work
Maybe we find cars, but
We will not get to the plane before dark
We have to Ntmask little longer
How we can stick to it? boss
I mean, at least this guy has
Plan give us the opportunity to fight
What are you talking about?
What about the, and ?
I've already lost a family member
I can not lose another
boss
I used to follow you to hell and back
you know that
But unfortunately
One day you're mistaken
It is right Aaoba
We can not have access to that plane
Before nightfall
This is our chance may be the only
Do you want to go
Go
Do you want to die
Go Humic
,osamaa O
I know that all of this is causing you to panic
We all
But we try, right?
How can you give up just like that?
What about the, I mean why
All these people, they are our family now?
You know?
I like you so much, ?
Believing that somehow we can
Survive this
And now
I feel that sacrifices must be made
What ?
, You, O God
We are waiting for what is inevitable here, right?
It is
I've made a decision, I do not want any of those things
To be standing over me and I
Shoot the last breath
I may not be able to defeat them
But I will not sit here and not do anything too
Is this good ?
it is good
, You know, when you and your grandmother and
And I said I'll take care of you both
I'm doing this for us,
do you understand me ?
I know
Come here, man
I want you to take care of your mother for me
You hear?
Hello Aaoba
Do you remember when we were kids?
, You tell us stories about
Young and Gzach
, Arrived at the
And Oohayoa, during the Civil War
This is beyond the conclusion reached by the Federal
Deported tens of thousands of federal
Their duties
But the South lost the war
And and Gzach, were slaughtered all
Yeah
They were slaughtered
But not at the time
Hear me, Dad
I know that the situation was different
Since the death of, I know
But it is worth
I want you to know that I unfortunately
For I am from survived
! Ooooh, Otia Ki Todeina
this is beautiful
! See you later alligator O
Do not do this, O ?
knows he does, right?
It has a plan
Oh really ?
Qublana and stay
, I am serious about my
me too
see you later
At the end of the street, there is a stop sign
Pierced Bostha lead
It's 300-yard marker
The following wind passing of these buildings
Mass occur in Rsasata
So, if you find yourselves in trouble
Go back to that mark
And Soguetakm Highest
Move these people we must
Find some cars
And you, Restart the front door camera
Aazeim aware
I'm going to matter -I Samatoh
On any given day we are?
Twenty-seventh of July
! I thought so
Why ?
Holiday birthday my son two days from now
Send him a card every year but
! Do not I receive anything from him
National Guard have done what they can to protect us
When we were heading to the hotel
They fought the last battle
They did not realize that they are raising meat
Somewhere like buffet
Persevered for two days
Yes, I wanted to go there myself to
We all wanted to do
Fortunately, convinced me To reverse it
And they kept us all together
When he brought because of leadership during the dregs
When he started the plague
it is true? -Right
He is with us from the time
on the other side we found
wandering around the city's semi-nude starving
To appreciate what I was writing a story
In fact the best
Battalion his own
Trod airlines outside Moscow
And cut off all the way to the
The Hadthia down, right? -Right
O man, You, can fight
Drink but could you fly planes -Why is it?
Do not worry my friend, if you live
In Russia, I want to get out of them too
They will be in place over the darkness
And deeper in this place
the basement
exactly
There where Sndvenhm
Listen, lose yourselves
There may be no way out
Turned to light
You two to the surface
Sntafrq
To the surface
We'll run away from there
How is it going abroad, Yakom
Any luck?
la Thing after
Nothing I have also
and I will separate
The situation does not seem good
Man, this place wornout
Why not increase your speed slightly
If we do not find means of transport
We can not get out of here
Did you understand that ? -
Aware of it -
Keep explosive charges
Every exits
The reserve these fucks here
Nshakhm and make them burn
It will put the bomb on the other filmmaker?
Let me do it
I am serious
I can do that
I want to do it
I do not mean the pressure you
But everything on your shoulders
Only Atvsd it, OK
Come
Does not issue voice
! Moved
Come on, come
Where ?
I said, Where ?
We ended up -What?
What are you talking about right?
How can ended O ?
What ?
! I've ended up, Just go only
How can you talk about the hell?
Damn, damn
Move
I think they are trying behind ?
I Do Taatleghana?
I, you Taatleghana?
Otrcna, Man,
I am in very poor condition
They are totally behind me and will enter
listen to me, Keep motionless probably find
A way to find you, just keep your place
No, you're too late, Just Say
For, I love them
Nocohesion O
I am coming to you, can you hear me?
You will need to pregnant?
I think I completely Osfielkm
I'll try to
listen to me
When the sun goes down
They will attack us fucks
Again, Man,
We need the rope
We need the dreaded cord
has a cord, I think
It is completely beneath us
Hey, wait a minute
This thing was seeking Here
All the time, right?
! It seeks Here you
! You
do you want me ?
Come
Come, O son of whores
let's go
Go
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on
Carried Zkherta
Damn
We will link it so peace
what is the problem? -We have to go
! I will not go anywhere
bit me
What good friends, right?
, Man, God you
Come on, take a look at this, man
I think I'll sit
I'll tell you something there is a bright side
At least, do not touch upon the eating
By those things
To lay resting my friend
, received one, I found a car
Well done Aavtah
Udi come here off
I will be here
It seems you were not the only
Able to find a princess car
It is not enough
what are you talking about ?
I mean, it is not enough, we have more than 40 people here
Well, the heck of it, we will take
What we can take
Each advocate for himself now a man
Why I came back here to hell?
Because I am not capable of leading the damned plane
O car ride, let's ride the car -
Oh, You scum -
O Let us, for we leave from here really
Dear scum
It is not riding the car
-hia O -I won't
Curse
Now we're talking
my dear -
Come on -
I think that all of you bastard Sikvana
Hurrah
One does not need to connect?
Hurrah dear
Yes, Hurrah
Coming
Come to the inside
Arise, be gone
Come on, come
We have to go
Dear leader, now
No
Come on, come on, come on
Where is my husband?
It has caused deaths in all of them, right?
! I did not ask anyone to go with me
It should be lying
There with them
For my son here
Now, not for you, you
He chose to come
At least he had the audacity
To go with me
Hey -O leader, not
-boss -Curse
Okhrsoa, you both Okhrsoa
I agreed, no one utter a word
damn you
We have to find a solution so
Or we will all here
And what do the hell?
We can not fight all these damned things
Fire has been fired at that thing
three times
Directly in the chest
But he continued to come
Maybe Okhtota in correction -
Not sinned -
I think it is different from others
It just does not die
Everything dies
O scum
Oh my God
They are everywhere
Will not be able to cross all this number never
Heck, look
dreaded
How you can do the hell?
He is trying to escape
It will not last 30 seconds abroad
Not a chance to display
We can exploit
Your taste?
Damn
Let me say it, old man
Those things will be back here soon
Are you ready to do this confrontation
These are your people abroad
, They need you
It's no secret that I do not like to lose the battle
I did not do and will never do
Not in the face of one nor anything
Especially, when there is something
Worth fighting for
This is all Maatmthelh this battle
People
And survival
So, it is very simple Yakom
If you maintain this row
All people will live Oalaik
If we do not, if we fail
All die
He is right
If ye ye would that survive these people
It is up to you
Make something of value
We'll see each other again, Aazeim
Thank you for your stay
Your girl ?
how are you ?
It was perfect
! They were all
And the to kill her
We have around
I can not leave them so
wait
I want to stay
Let me help you
That did not get out of here?
These people will need to someone
Someone to lead them
Someone who has hope
Curse
A good, we are ready, my dear
We agreed ?
Sorry
I love you
You will not come with us, right?
There are still more of them abroad
But you killed him?
Killed the, is not that
You makint want?
,thompski Hope so, oh
,??? ??? ?? (????)
translation @Fahood_qahtany
0557669038